Rice juggled it all for Naughty eventually held
on but the play comes back off the offensive
holding call.
On first and 20,
Mahomes steps up on the run and look who's wide open.
It's Kelsey.
And he lowers the shoulder at the Raider 40.
Play was the longest of the season for Travis.
Here's a second and five.
Down in the field and it's Noah Gray.
The backup tied in with another big pass play.
Here's first and goal.
Hunt is the running back.
And they bring it back around.
And they toss it to him.
It's Rice cutting through and he's in the end zone for a touchdown.
We do have a flag down.
A flag back at the line of scrimmage.
Spiraling this one too much, Tony.
I think I could have gone in there and done that and then he
gonna have to pay for that football.
I think on Monday, but
other than that,
there's the face mask right there.
He fought
right through it too.
And you can see all the emotions of
getting back out here.
And there's Kareem Hunt getting
rolled up right there.
They had Trace Smith was also third and
eight.
Pass caught and pushed out about three yards short of
the first.
That was Besh with the reception.
Wow. Scary.
Second
and 10. There's Worthy.
We're about seven or eight and pushed
back by Chen.
Producer today, Trace.
How nice of him.
What a
good guy.
Someone's gonna get lucky with him.
Third and two.
There is Rice.
Back steps and gets the first down at about the
31. Second year for Callahan overall as they go to Rice.
Sorry.
Mahomes says,
coach, it doesn't work.
He was faking it.
There they go.
They picked up a good one there.
It was right in
Mahomes face when he launched it.
Second and 10
to Smith.
The
rookies got a running start.
He's got a first down on first
and 10. Him on it.
Watch right here.
Rice.
Boom.
Mahomes runs it.
Slides for a first down.
He was their leading rusher coming into the week on the season.
Worthy came back.
Everyone
got to do what they are good at doing.
You don't have to put guys in position to do stuff
they're not good at.
First and 10. At the five yard line,
it's hauled in on the rebound.
That's it.
Mahomes
down the middle and he's got him.
Hollywood for the touchdown.
You're gonna get one on one right here because
everyone else is pressuring.
And then when you have all the weapons out there,
Jim,
you
can find your best matchup.
But it's.
Gino.
He had to commit to it.
He got past the line
and he falls.
Can they pick up what would be only the third first down of the game?
Smith.
Jones has got him at the 31.
When he came in first on the scene as a rookie.
Fake it to him here.
And now Mahomes fakes
everybody like he's gonna pass it and goes out of bounds so far.
Versus only 14 for the
Raiders.
Quickly tossed over to Smith.
Smith breaks a tackle and almost was able to break
it.
That's Jeremy Chin, who got him by the ankles.
He's in a tough position.
Three man
rush right here.
One's a spy standing up.
Third and four it is.
Spied into his job.
He's got
it again.
Scrabble for another first.
Some good short yardage calls, I guess.
That's
impressive.
Second and 10. There's Rice.
That was a no look.
How about that?
Down the middle.
It is caught.
Juju Smith Schuster.
You see the tight splits.
You have a two way go with Rice.
You can do anything here.
First looks at rice and then goes to
Smith Schuster down to the three yard line.
But you have no
timeouts.
I would act.
You have to throw it.
Looks left,
throws left and it is caught by Rice for his second
touchdown of the game.
They're so difficult.
Rice goes inside.
He plays in the slot,
plays the tight end type position, gets outside,
runs a back shoulder fade
on the red zone against
Kelly.
And the reason.
Let's see with Gino and company.
They go out of the gun and they hand it
off to Gentie to close out the half.
Gentie's fourth carry for 18 yards in the half.
Because it's third and 14. You have not made a single stop all
day.
Not seen a rise upon to this point.
Smith.
Out here to improve and get better.
You feel like you're going to win the game.
But don't make any mistakes.
Make it a simple play call like
this.
Over to Rice.
Near the first.
The safeties are too deep for third and one.
To
the flat.
Fake to Hunt and they go right back to a wide out.
The
ball comes up and it's scooped up.
Brown fumbled it and then
Worthy was on the spot.
Not going to keep two safeties back.
First down.
And rolled out with it.
Across the body.
Look out.
Caught somehow.
That's Worthy.
It was a jump ball.
We do have
Hollywood Brown.
There you go.
Hands off.
Look at this.
Button
heads down to the six.
By the way, you saw Worthy shaking up on
the sideline.
Pacheco races.
We have a flag in the end zone.
It's a touchdown for the moment by Pacheco.
You see guys trying
to get all lined up.
They're too late.
Then the movement up front
and Pacheco has been running.
Another complete player come back
and that's dangerous.
First down.
Mahone steps up and launches open.
And is caught on his back.
Ty Kwan.
Thornton.
He's up to 283 yards passing.
Here comes Worthy.
From off the bench to running it on the end
of the line.
And it's a round for another first and a gain of
12. Kelsey is one on one on the left if you want him.
And
incomplete.
In the area of Brown.
That's a better stop than
the other non-stops.
Kick is good from 38. He's six out of
11 yards.
Boot leg.
He's got a completion.
Break the streak.
The
Chiefs win it 1917. Third and 16. To Jentee.
Slips through a
tackle.
And boy,
fought through Chimari Conner to get within a
couple.
With Hank Stram
and Lynn Dawson.
Hall of Famers.
Just went
ahead of him with this one today.
It's going to be the 93rd.
And still at two first downs.
And we're in the fourth quarter.
Pass.
Did that hit the ground or is that caught?
Looks like a
catch on the field.
You ruined it for me.
You know the defense
did pitch a shutout that day.
They're in on him.
Somehow he
got the pass away incomplete.
I'm doing the math now.
I'm
starting to get it.
Connecting the dots.
For the first down on
third and four is Smith.
That's six championships between the
two of them total.
And out to the 50 yard line on what was a
third and 11 during the preseason.
And he fumbles the
snap.
It's a fumble and it's recovered by Kansas City.
Every one of those teams is good.
On third down they're going to
stay on the ground.
And Smith takes it to about the five.
If
the Chiefs go undefeated in that stretch,
Jim. Like you could in
some years.
100%. Here's a fourth down run.
That was nice.
And they stop him.
I don't want to take away from Andy.
That was
right there.
But it's just one of those where you hope he can
turn around.
We root for a lot of guys without with impartiality.
Obviously involved in it.
That's Loughby who had cared at the
previous play and ready to play today and they played
at a very
high level on both sides of the ball.
That was complimentary
football all the way across.
Give the Chiefs credit for
bringing it today.
Coming up again, the State Farm Post Game
Show.
J.B.
Mahomes and he's got things in there is crossing all
sports.
And
he's got ties to.
That hole already put up another excellent performance here.
It looked like it was deflating from that point forward.
This is literally,
we're going to look this up after.
The number of plays,
if this is the last play of the game,
Jim,
it's 29.
29 for Vegas.
Total.
I'm shocked it's not one,
but that's what they had.
They've got to go in a buy.
They've got to live with the
stench of this one for two weeks.
They need to have time to
figure something out.
Two legendary coaches right there.
Hall of Famers.